Waymo One
    
    The world’s first autonomous ride-hailing service

    Waymo Driver
    
    The World’s Most Experienced Driver™

    Company
    
    Our mission: Be the world’s most trusted driver

    Safety
    
    Because Safety is Urgent™

    Community
    
    Supporting and empowering communities

    Careers
    
    Find your drive

Waymo Web Privacy Policy
========================

Effective Date: February 20, 2018
---------------------------------

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Waymo LLC and its subsidiaries ("Waymo"). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our websites and other products and services that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "Services"). We may supply a different privacy policy in relation to some of our Services, and that policy will apply to any information provided to or collected by us pursuant to those Services.We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you a notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

Collection of Information
-------------------------

### Information You Provide to Us

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you participate in any interactive features of the Services, fill out a form, provide feedback, participate in a contest or promotion, apply for a job, communicate with us via third party sites, request customer support, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, and any other information you choose to provide.

### Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services

When you access or use our Services, we may automatically collect information about you, including:

* **Log Information:** We may collect log information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address, and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.
    
* **Information Collected by Cookies:** Like many websites, we may use cookies to collect information about visitors and visits to our Site. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular, and count visits. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see "Your Choices" below.

### Information We Collect From Other Sources

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including but not limited to identity verification services and publicly available sources.

Use of Information
------------------

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to:

* Provide, maintain and improve our Services;
    
* Provide and deliver the products and services you request, and send you related information;
    
* Respond to your comments, questions, and requests and provide customer service;
    
* Communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events offered by Waymo and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
    
* Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Services;
    
* Detect, investigate, and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of Waymo and others;
    
* Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content, or features that match user profiles or interests;
    
* Facilitate contests, sweepstakes, and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards;
    
* Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and
    
* Carry out any other purpose described to you at the time the information was collected.

How We Disclose Your Information
--------------------------------

We only disclose your personal information in a few limited cases described below. We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.Waymo will not disclose your personal information with a third party unless one of the following applies:

* You give us or them consent
    
* They are performing a service for us, such as to process payments, help analyze and improve our services, conduct surveys, deliver ads or send emails on our behalf
    
* We're involved in a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale or transfer of some or all of our assets
    
* In order to tailor products, services, ads, and offers to your interests as detailed in our U.S. state law requirements section below.
    
* Other legal and business reasons when required, or to:
    
    * Comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request
        
    * Enforce our customer agreements, including to investigate potential violations
        
    * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues
        
    * Protect the rights, property, or safety of Waymo, our customers, or others, as required or permitted by applicable laws.

Some of our products let you share data to services provided by other companies. We don't control the data collection and use practices of these other services. To learn more, please visit the privacy policies of the companies that provide these services.

Social Sharing Features
-----------------------

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools, which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others
-----------------------------------------------------

We may allow others to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and in applications. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites and applications, including your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Waymo and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

Security
--------

Waymo takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

Transfer of Information to the U.S. and Other Countries
-------------------------------------------------------

Waymo is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing, transfer and storage of information in and to the U.S. and other countries, where you may not have the same rights and protections as you do under local law.

Your Choices
------------

### Cookies

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.

### Promotional Communications

You may opt out of receiving promotional messages from Waymo by following the instructions in those messages. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as those about our ongoing business relations.

U.S. State Law Requirements
---------------------------

Some U.S. state privacy laws like the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) and Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (VCDPA) require specific disclosures for state residents. We describe the choices you have to manage your privacy and data across Waymo’s services in [Your choices](https://support.google.com/waymo/answer/9184840#zippy=%2Cinformation-we-collect%2Chow-we-use-it%2Cwhat-we-keep%2Cyour-choices). You can exercise your rights by using these controls, which allow you to access, review, update and delete your information, as well as, [export and download](https://support.google.com/waymo/answer/9681942) a copy of it. If you have questions or requests related to your rights under state privacy laws, you (or your authorized agent) can also contact Waymo using this [Help page](https://support.google.com/waymo/answer/9681942) or by calling us at 1-844-261-3753.Subject to certain limits and exceptions, California residents have certain rights with respect to their data as follows:

* Right of Access: You may ask us to confirm whether we are processing your personal information and, if so, to provide you with a copy of the personal information we hold about you (along with certain other details).
    
* Right to Correction: If the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to ask for correction or completion.
    
* Right to Deletion: You may ask us to delete or remove your personal information in some circumstances—for example, if we no longer need it.
    
* Right to Opt-Out of “sales”, “sharing” and “targeted advertising”. You can opt out of these activities by following the link at [Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information](https://waymo.com/privacy/#do-not-track).
    
* Right to Limit Use of Sensitive Personal Information: Waymo does not use or disclose sensitive personal information for any purpose other than as permitted by the law without right to limit.
    
* Right to be free from Discrimination in connection with exercising any of the foregoing rights.

### Additional Information for California Residents

The CCPA, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act, affords individuals residing in California certain rights with respect to their personal information. If you are a California resident, this section applies to you.We collect, use and disclose your personal information in the following ways:

| Categories of personal information we collect | Business purposes for which personal information may be used or disclosed | Parties with whom personal information may be disclosed |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identifier and similar information, such as your name and password, phone number, email, and address, as well as unique identifiers tied to the browser, application, or device you’re using. | Protecting against security threats, abuse, and illegal activity, such as to detect, investigate, prevent and address fraud, vehicle collisions, complaints, disputes, violations of our customer agreements and other illegal activity; and to protect the rights, safety and property of Waymo and others. | Other people with whom you choose to share your information, like if you want us to send information about your trip to another person or Waymo customer. |
| Demographic information, such as age, gender, language, and size of household. | Auditing and measurement: Waymo uses information for analytics and measurement to understand how our services and products are used. We may disclose aggregate information publicly and with certain partners, including for auditing purposes. | Third parties with your consent such as services that integrate with Waymo services. |
| Sensitive personal information, which may include personal identification numbers (such as government-issued identification), precise geolocation, racial or ethnic origin, veteran status, sexual orientation, and personal data collected and analyzed concerning your health (e.g., disability status). | Maintaining our services: Waymo uses information to ensure our services are working as intended, such as tracking outages or troubleshooting bugs and other issues that you report to us. | Service providers, trusted businesses or persons that process information on Waymo’s behalf, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. |
| Commercial information, such as your payment method and billing address. | Research and development: Waymo uses information to improve our services and to develop new products, features and technologies. | Law enforcement or other third parties, for the legal reasons described in How we share the information we collect. |
| Internet, network, and other activity information, such as views, access times, and interactions with content and our apps; referrer URL when you use our products; the device you use to access our app, including hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, device event information (such as crashes, hardware settings, and the date and time of your request); in-vehicle interfaces; and wireless and/or mobile network information. | Use of service providers: Waymo shares information with service providers to perform services on our behalf, in compliance with our Privacy Policy and other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. | Merger or acquisition: In the event of a reorganization, merger, financing transaction, corporate reorganization, sale of company assets or acquisition, we may share any and all personal information we collect with the relevant third party. |
| Geolocation data, which may be determined by GPS, IP address, and other data from sensors on or around your device, depending in part on your device and app settings. With your permission, we also collect the precise location of your mobile device. We also collect pickup and drop-off location, details about the vehicle’s route and device location information during a trip. | Communicate with you about service and account notices and features, offers, news and other information we think will be of interest to you. |     |
| Communications data, such as emails, if you use our services to send and receive messages. | Personalization: Waymo processes information, including online identifiers and information about your interactions with products and services, to personalize your experience, including any ads or other information you see when you use our products and services. |     |
| Audio, electronic, visual and similar information, such as your Google profile picture, video recorded inside the vehicle during trips, and audio recording during active voice calls with our support teams. Please visit our Help Center for more information. | Facilitate contests, sweepstakes, and promotions: If you choose to participate, Waymo uses information to process and deliver entries and rewards. |     |
| Professional, employment, and education information: such as information you provide including education information and employment details. | Legal reasons: Waymo also uses information to satisfy applicable laws or regulations, and discloses information as required by regulation or in response to legal process or enforceable government requests, including to law enforcement. |     |
| Other information you create or provide, such as when you fill out a form, use interactive features, provide feedback, participate in a contest or promotion, request customer support, create content, or otherwise communicate with us. |     |     |
| Inferences drawn from the above such as understanding frequently visited destinations, determining new or optimal drop-off and pickup locations, suggesting destinations, and personalizing your experience, including any ads or other information you see when you use our products and services. |     |     |

### Right to Opt Out of Sharing, Disclosure, or Sale of Personal Information

Waymo may “share” and “sell” identifiers and electronic network activity information, as those terms are defined in the CCPA, with advertising partners (including social media platforms) to tailor products, services, ads, and offers to your interests. You can disable some types of cookies and opt to stop “sharing” and “selling” your information [here](https://waymo.com/privacy/#do-not-track). You can also opt out of certain targeted advertising, sharing and sales by visiting our websites or mobile apps with a recognized universal choice signal enabled (such as the Global Privacy Control). Please note that, depending on which opt-out preference signal you use \[and whether you are logged into your account with us\], our processing of the signal may be limited to the specific browser or device that you are using. You may need to renew your opt-out if you use a different browser or device to access our Services. We do not knowingly “share” or “sell” personal information about consumers under the age of 16.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@waymo.com](mailto:privacy@waymo.com).

Changes to this Policy
----------------------

We may change this policy from time to time. We will post any changes to this policy on this page. Each version of this policy is identified at the top of the page by its effective date.

Last updated: January 1, 2023

Sign up for updates to get the latest on Waymo.

Select language English Español Filipino 中文（简体中文） 中文（繁體中文）

* * *

Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information

Waymo may disclose user personal information to third parties to tailor advertising and offers to your interests. Such disclosures may be considered “sales” or “sharing” of personal information under the laws described above. California residents may opt-out of these below. If you opt out, Waymo will not disclose your personal information to third parties for purposes of tailoring advertising or offers to your interests. Note that any choice you make here will **only affect this website on this browser and device**. To learn more about how your data is shared, view our [Privacy Policy page](https://waymo.com/privacy/).

© 2019-2024 Waymo LLC
